Frank G. Speck Papers 1903-1950 Mss.Ms.Coll.126
American Philosophical Society
- Subcollection I. Frank G. Speck Papers, 1897-1950; 10 linear feet
  - Series III. Photographs, 1904-1950; 572.97 Sp3
    - Florida and Louisiana (Non-Native American), 12-12(a-o)
    - Formosa, n.d.; 12-13(a-5, b-7, c-7)
    - India, 12-14(a-b)
    - Laps (Finland), 12-15(a-j)
    - Maine, trips to Northern #1, 1925; 12-16(a-p)
    - Maine, trips to Northern #2, 1925; 12-17(a-r)
    - Maine, trips to Northern #3, 1925; 12-18(a-w)
    - Maine, trips to Northern #4, 1925; 12-19(a-t)
    - Maine, trips to Northern #5, 1919-1931; 12-20(a-r)
    - Maori #1, n.d.; 12-21(a-k)
    - Maori #2, n.d.; 12-22(a-l)
    - Maori #3, n.d.; 12-23(a-l)
    - Maori #4, n.d.; 12-24(a-l)
    - Maori #5, n.d.; 12-25(a-l)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d.; 12-26(a-p)
    - Mongoloid race types, n.d.; 12-27(a-b)
    - Natural history #1, n.d.; 12-28(a-p)
    - Natural history #2, n.d.; 12-29(a-t)
    - New Hampshire, n.d.; 12-30(a-g)
    - New Jersey, Pine Barrens #1, 1919; 12-31(a-p)
    - New Jersey, Pine Barrens #2, 1919; 12-32(a-n)
    - New Jersey, Pine Barrens #3, 1919; 12-33(a-r)
    - Oceania, 1938; 12-34(a-b)
    - Philippine, 1908-1932; 12-35(a-d)
    - Sakai (Malay Peninsula), 1906; 12-36(a)
    - Speck, Frank G.--childhood drawings, n.d.; 12-37(a-i)
    - Tigre, n.d.; 12-38(a-b)
    - Watermelon Feast, n.d.; 12-39(a)
    - Zulu #1, 1895; 12-40(a-f)
    - Zulu #2, 1930; 12-41(a-i)
  - Series IV. Lantern Slides, 1914-1938
    - Candelaria, the Belle of the Seri, Lower California, 1914-1938; 13:1-1-a; Box 1: Baja California, #001
    - Demasduit or Waunatoake (Mary March), 1914-1938; 13:1-2-a; Box 1: Beothuk, #002
    - Beothuk man, 1914-1938; 13:1-2-b; Box 1: Beothuk, #003
    - Beothuk family, 1914-1938; 13:1-2-c; Box 1: Beothuk, #004
    - Beothuk man and woman, 1914-1938; 13:1-2-d; Box 1: Beothuk, #005
    - Map of Newfoundland, 1914-1938; 13:1-3-a; Box 1: Canada, #006
    - Landscape, 1914-1938; 13:1-3-b; Box 1: Canada, #007
    - Preparing a seal, 1914-1938; 13:1-3-c; Box 1: Canada, #008
    - Native American settlement, 1914-1938; 13:1-3-d; Box 1: Canada, #009
    - Native American dwelling, 1914-1938; 13:1-3-e; Box 1: Canada, #010
    - Landscape, 1914-1938; 13:1-3-f; Box 1: Canada, #011
    - Native Americans hunting, 1914-1938; 13:1-3-g; Box 1: Canada, #012
    - Tipi and canoe, 1914-1938; 13:1-3-h; Box 1: Canada, #013
    - Home of Sally Brown, Catawba Reservation, S.C., 1936; 13:1-4-a; Box 1: Catawba, #014
    - Sally Brown preparing sedge-grass for making brooms, Catawba, S.C., 1938; 13:1-4-b; Box 1: Catawba, #015
    - Sally Brown Gordon, one of the last speakers of Catawba, 1936; 13:1-4-c; Box 1: Catawba, #016
    - Sally Brown and family, Catawba, S.C., 1936; 13:1-4-d; Box 1: Catawba, #017
    - Catawba man, 1914-1938; 13:1-4-e; Box 1: Catawba, #018
    - Catawba man, 1914-1938; 13:1-4-f; Box 1: Catawba, #019
    - Lydia's Father and Mother, 1914-1938; 13:1-4-g; Box 1: Catawba, #020
    - Suzan Owl, Catawba, Cherokee, N.C., 1914-1938; 13:1-4-h; Box 1: Catawba, #021
    - Mrs. Samson Owl, Catawba, Cherokee Nation, N.C., 1922; 13:1-4-i; Box 1: Catawba, #022
    - Eliza Stamper, Cherokee, N.C., 1915; 13:1-5-a; Box 1: Cherokee, #023
    - Cross arrow game, Cherokee, N.C., 1915-1948; 13:1-5-b; Box 1: Cherokee, #024
    - Cross arrow game, Cherokee, N.C., 1915-1948; 13:1-5-c; Box 1: Cherokee, #025
    - Booger mask of wasp nest, Big Cove, Cherokee, 1915-1948; 13:1-5-d; Box 1: Cherokee, #026
    - Child, Cherokee, N.C., 1915-1948; 13:1-5-e; Box 1: Cherokee, #027
    - Women's leg rattles, Cherokee, N.C., 1915-1948; 13:1-5-f; Box 1: Cherokee, #028
    - Winter settlement, Cherokee, N.C., 1915-1948; 13:1-5-g; Box 1: Cherokee, #029
    - Eagle dance, Cherokee, N.C., 1915-1948; 13:1-5-h; Box 1: Cherokee, #030
    - Eagle dance, Cherokee, N.C., 1915-1948; 13:1-5-i; Box 1: Cherokee, #031
    - Eagle dance, Cherokee, N.C., 1915-1948; 13:1-5-j; Box 1: Cherokee, #032
    - Mother and child, Cherokee, N.C., 1915-1948; 13:1-5-k; Box 1: Cherokee, #033
    - John and Nanny Driver and family, Cherokee, N.C., 1915-1948; 13:1-5-l; Box 1: Cherokee, #034
    - Cherokee child, Cherokee, N.C., 1915-1948; 13:1-5-m; Box 1: Cherokee, #035
    - Landscape, Cherokee, N.C., 1915-1948; 13:1-5-n; Box 1: Cherokee, #036
    - Landscape, Cherokee, N.C., 1915-1948; 13:1-5-o; Box 1: Cherokee, #037
    - Landscape, Cherokee, N.C., 1915-1948; 13:1-5-p; Box 1: Cherokee, #038
    - Landscape, Cherokee, N.C., 1914-1948; 13:1-5-q; Box 1: Cherokee. #039
    - Landscape, Cherokee, N.C., 1915-1948; 13:1-5-r; Box 1: Cherokee, #040
    - Landscape, Cherokee, N.C., 1914-1948; 13:1-5-s; Box 1: Cherokee, #041
    - Winter settlement, Cherokee, N.C., 1914-1948; 13:1-5-t; Box 1: Cherokee, #042
    - John Driver's family, Cherokee, N.C., 1914-1948; 13:1-5-u; Box 1: Cherokee, #043
    - Tawnita, Cherokee, N.C., 1914; 13:1-5-v; Box 1: Cherokee, #044
    - Canoe, Cherokee, N.C., 1915-1948; 13:1-5-w; Box 1: Cherokee, #045
    - Settlement, Cherokee, N.C., 1914-1948; 13:1-5-x; Box 1: Cherokee, #046
    - Landscape, Cherokee, N.C., 1914-1948; 13:1-5-y; Box 1: Cherokee, #047
    - Crossing the river, Cherokee, N.C., 1914-1948; 13:1-5-z; Box 1: Cherokee, #048
    - Mortar and pestle, 1915-1948; 13:1-5-aa; Box 1: Cherokee, #049
    - Ball game, 1904; 13:1-6-a; Box 2: Creek and Yuchi, #050
    - Ball game, 1904; 13:1-6-b; Box 2: Creek and Yuchi, #051
    - Man, 1904; 13:1-6-c; Box 2: Creek and Yuchi, #052
    - Men and women, 1904; 13:1-6-d; Box 2: Creek and Yuchi, #053
    - Dwelling, 1904; 13:1-6-e; Box 2: Creek and Yuchi, #054
    - Children, 1904; 13:1-6-f; Box 2: Creek and Yuchi, #055
    - Yuchi family (Oklahoma), 1904; 13:1-6-g; Box 2: Creek and Yuchi, #056
    - Creek family, 1904; 13:1-6-h; Box 2: Creek and Yuchi, #057
    - Creek man, portrait, Oklahoma, 1904; 13:1-6-i; Box 2: Creek and Yuchi, #058
    - Yuchi woman, portrait, Oklahoma, 1903; 13:1-6-j; Box 2: Creek and Yuchi, #059
    - Yuchi woman, portrait, Oklahoma, 1903; 13:1-6-k; Box 2: Creek and Yuchi, #060
    - Man in native attire, 1904; 13:1-6-l; Box 2: Creek and Yuchi, #061
    - Allegoo (Shining water), Sikoslingmuit Eskimo woman, Southern Baffin Land, 1901-1947; 13:1-7-a; Box 2: Eskimo, #062
    - Eskimo children, 1901-1947; 13:1-7-b; Box 2: Eskimo, #063
    - Native woman, Greenland, 1901-1947; 13:1-7-c; Box 2: Eskimo, #064
    - House of Palmetto, near Golden Meadow, La., 1938-1939; 13:1-8-a; Box 2: Houma, #065
    - Chimney, Palmetto house, La., 1938-1939; 13:1-8-b; Box 2: Houma, #066
    - Dwelling, 1938-1939; 13:1-8-c; Box 2: Houma, #067
    - Interior of Palmetto hut, roof, 1938-1939; 13:1-8-d; Box 2: Houma, #068
    - Vegetation, 1938-1939; 13:1-8-e; Box 2: Houma, #069
    - Man with fishing net, 1938-1939; 13:1-8-f; Box 2: Houma, #070
    - Man with fishing net, 1938-1939; 13:1-8-g; Box 2: Houma, #071
    - Canoe, 1938-1939; 13:1-8-h; Box 2: Houma, #072
    - Bayou Grand Caillou, Louisiana, 1938-1939; 13:1-8-i; Box 2: Houma, #073
    - Bayou Grand Caillou, Louisiana, 1938-1939; 13:1-8-j; Box 2: Houma, #074
    - Dwelling, 1938-1939; 13:1-8-k; Box 2: Houma, #075
    - Men and women in canoes, 1938-1939; 13:1-8-l; Box 2: Houma, #076
    - Geese outside thatched roof dwelling, 1938-1939; 13:1-8-m; Box 2< Houma, #077
    - Children with mortar and pestle, 13:1-8-n; Box 2: Houma, #078
    - Man with tool, 1938-1939; 13:1-8-o; Box 2: Houma, #079
    - Map of tribal boundaries, Southeast, U.S., 1938-1939; 13:1-8-p; Box 2: Houma, #080
    - Forest, 1938-1939; 13:1-8-q; Box 2: Houma, #081
    - Palmetto house near Bourge, Louisiana, 1938-1939; 13:1-8-r; Box 2: Houma, #082
    - Palmetto house, Louisiana, 1938-1939; 13:1-8-s; Box 2: houma, #083
    - Houma girl, 1938-1939; 13:1-8-t; Box 2: Houma, #084
    - Couple outside palmetto house, 1938-1939; 13:1-8-u; Box 2: Houma, #085
    - Man outside palmetto house, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-a; Box 2: Houma, #086
    - Dwelling, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-b; Box 2: Houma, #087
    - Dwelling, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-c; Box 2: Houma, #088
    - Man in canoe, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-d; Box 2: Houma, #089
    - Vegetation, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-e; Box 2: Houma, #090
    - Dwellings, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-f; Box 2: Houma, #091
    - Settlement with men, women and children, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-g; Box 2: Houma, #092
    - Houma man, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-h; Box 2: Houma, #093
    - Map, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-i; Box 2: Houma, #094
    - Interior of Palmetto hut, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-j; Box 2: Houma, #095
    - Woman and child, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-k; Box 2: Houma, #096
    - Houma boy, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-l; Box 2: Houma, #097
    - Man in canoe, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-m; Box 2: houma, #098
    - Houma couple, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-n; Box 2: Houma, #099
    - Man outside palmetto house, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-o; Box 2: Houma, #100
    - Houma man in canoe, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-p; Box 3: Houma, #101
    - Landscape, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-q; Box 3: Houma, #102
    - Houma woman and girl, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-r; Box 3: Houma, #103
    - Houma man with two children, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-s; Box 3: Houma, #104
    - Landscape with Houma dwelling, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-t; Box 2: Houma, #105
    - Houma children, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-u; Box 3: Houma, #106
    - Houma man, 1938-1939; 13:1-9-v; Box 3: Houma, #107
    - Skeletal remains, Hughes site, Maryland, 13:1-10-a; Box 3: Hughes site, MD, #108
    - Skeletal remains, Hughes site, Maryland, 13:1-10-b; Box 3: Hughes site, MD, #109
    - Mr. and Mrs. Roncoe's store, Indian Island, Maine, 1906-1941; 13:1-11-a; Box 3: Indian Island, ME, #110
    - Oldest woman and Louisa, Indian Island, Maine, 1906-1941; 13:1-11-b; Box 3: Indian Island, ME, #111
    - Penobscot family in canoe, 1906-1941; 13:1-11-c; Box 3: Indian Island, ME, #112
    - Penobscot women and children, 1906-1941; 13:1-11-d; Box 3: Indian Island, ME, #113
    - Penobscot family, 1906-1941; 13:1-11-e; Box 3: Indian Island, ME, #114
    - Penobscot men carrying canoe, 1906-1941; 13:1-11-h; Box 3: Indian Island, ME, #115
    - Penobscot family, canoe on water, 1906-1941; 13:1-11-f; Box 3: Indian Island, ME, #116
    - Two Penobscot women, 1906-1941; 13:1-11-g; Box 3: Indian Island, ME, #117
    - Penobscot canoe on water, 1906-1941; 13:1-11-i; Box 3: Indian Island, ME, #118
    - Iroquois melodrama, 1906; 13:2-1-a; Box 3: Indian melodrama, #119
    - Iroquois melodrama, 1906; 13:2-1-b; Box 3: Indian melodrama, #120
    - Iroquois melodrama, 1906; 13:2-1-c; Box 3: Indian melodrama, #121
    - Iroquois melodrama, 1906; 13:2-1-d; Box 3: Indian melodrama, #122
    - Iroquois melodrama, 1906; 13:2-1-e; Box 3: Indian melodrama, #123
    - Iroquois melodrama, 1906; 13:2-1-f; Box 3: Indian melodrama, #124
    - Iroquois melodrama, 1906; 13:2-1-g; Box 3: Indian melodrama, #125
    - Iroquois melodrama, 1906; 13:2-1-h; Box 3: Indian melodrama, #126
    - Iroquois melodrama, 1906; 13:2-1-i; Box 3: Indian melodrama, #127
    - Iroquois melodrama, 1906; 13:2-1-j; Box 3: Indian melodrama, #128
    - Iroquois melodrama, 1906; 13:2-1-k; Box 3: Indian melodrama, #129
    - Iroquois melodrama, 1906; 13:2-1-l; Box 3: indian melodrama, #130
    - Iroquois melodrama, 1906; 13:2-1-m; Box 2: Indian melodrama, #131
    - Iroquois melodrama, 1906; 13:2-1-n; Box 3: Indian melodrama, #132
    - Huron boys, 1913-1952; 13:2-2-a; Box 3: Iroquois, #133
    - Peter Dibeau, Mohawk, Ripley, N.Y., 1904; 13:2-2-b; Box 3: Iroquois, #134
    - Seneca group, Cattaraugus, N.Y., 13:2-2-c; Box 3: Iroquois, #135
    - Archaeologist's camp, Cattaraugus, N.Y., 1904; 13:2-2-d; Box 3: Iroquois, #136
    - M. le Cure, Odanak, P.Q., 1913-1952; 13:2-2-e; Box 3: Iroquois, #137
    - Abenaki woman outside post office, Odanak, P.Q., 1913-1952; 13:2-2-f; Box 3: Iroquois, #138
    - Huron family outside dwelling, Loretteville, P.Q., 1913-1952; 13:2-2-g; Box 3: Iroquois, #139
    - Abenaki man tilling soil, Odanak, P.Q., 1913-1952; 13:2-2-h; Box 3: Iroquois, #140
    - Common pasture, Odanak, P.Q., 1913-1952; 13:2-2-i; Box 3: Iroquois, #141
    - Iroquois melodrama, 1906; 13:2-2-j; Box 3: Iroquois, #142
    - Iroquois woman, portrait, 1913-1952; 13:2-2-k; Box 3: Iroquois, #143
    - Virginia Hall, Hampton, 1913-1952; 13:2-2-l; Box 3: Iroquois, #144
    - Iroquois ball game, 1913-1952; 13:2-2-m; Box 3: Iroquois, #145
    - School children, Odanak, P.Q., 1913-1952; 13:2-2-n; Box 3: iroquois, #146
    - River scene, near Loretto, 1913-1952; 13:2-2-o; Box 3: Iroquois, #147
    - Convent, Odanak, P.Q., 1913-1952; 13:2-2-p; Box 3: Iroquois, #148
    - Abenaki women sewing, 1913-1952; 13:2-2-q; Box 3: Iroquois, #149
    - Abenaki brass band, Odanak, P.Q., 1913-1952; 13:2-2-r; Box 3: iroquois, #150
    - Church, Odanak, P.Q., 1913-1952; 13:2-2-s; Box 4: Iroquois, #151
    - Ferry Road, Odanak, P.Q., 1913-1952; 13:2-2-t; Box 4: Iroquois, #152
    - Mr. Puru, Storekeeper, Onanak, P.Q., 1913-1952; 13:2-2-u; Box 4: Iroquois, #153
    - Loretteville, P.Q., 1913-1952; 13:2-2-v; Box 4: Iroquois, #154
    - Landscape, Alleghany River, Reservation, 1913-1952; 13:2-2-w; Box 4: Iroquois, #155
    - School house, Onondaga, 1913-1952; 13:2-2-x; Box 4: Iroquois, #156
    - Portrait, Iroquois woman, 1913-1952; 13:2-2-y; Box 4: Iroquois, #157
    - School children, Onondaga reservation, 1913-1952; 13:2-2-z; Box 4: Iroquois, #158
    - Moses Wluto Hogansbury, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-a; Box 4: Iroquois, #159
    - Landscape, Alleghany River, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-b; Box 4: Iroquois, #160
    - Boy in doorway, store, Loretteville, P.Q., 1913-1952; 13:2-3-c; Box 4: Iroquois, #161
    - Group portrait, Onondaga, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-d; Box 4: Iroquois, #162
    - Waterfall, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-e; Box 4: iroquois, #163
    - Waterfall, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-f; Box 4: Iroquois, #164
    - Caughnawaga, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-g; Box 4: Iroquois, #165
    - Falls at St. Regis reservation, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-h; Box 4: Iroquois, #166
    - Plowing, Odanak, P.Q., 1913-1952; 13:2-3-i; Box 4: Iroquois, #167
    - Girl, Onondaga, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-j; Box 4: Iroquois, #168
    - Boy, Onondaga, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-k; Box 4: Iroquois, #169
    - Caughnawaga, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-l; Box 4:Iroquois, #170
    - Pere Gras quarters, Caughnawaga, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-m; Box 4: Iroquois, #171
    - Sir William Johnson's grave, Johnstown, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-n; Box 4: Iroquois, #172
    - House, interior, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-o; Box 4: Iroquois, #173
    - Moses Wluto Hogansbury's children, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-p; Box 4: Iroquois, #174
    - Caughnawaga children, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-q; Box 4: Iroquois, #175
    - First lilacs planted in America, Johnson Hall, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-r; Box 4: Iroquois, #176
    - Sir William Johnson, Johnstown, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-s; Box 4: Iroquois, #177
    - Rev. and Mrs. Louis Brun, St. Regis, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-t; Box 4: Iroquois, #178
    - St. Regis, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-u; Box 4: Iroquois, #179
    - The Indian dead, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-v; Box 4: Iroquois, #180
    - U.S. Custom house, 1913-1952; 13:2-3-w; Box 4: Iroquois, #181
    - Odanak, P.Q., 1913-1952; 13:2-3-x; Box 4: Iroquois, #182
    - Dolly Kick, Oneida, 1907; 13:2-3-y; Box 4: Iroquois, #183
    - Tipi, n.d.; 13:2-4-a; Box 4: Miscellaneous 1, #184
    - Group portrait, n.d.; 13:2-4-b; Box 4: Miscellaneous 1, #185
    - Head dress and pipe, 13:2-4-c; 13:2-5-k; Box 4: Miscellaneous 1, #186; #211
    - Native American man with pipe, drum, n.d.; 13:2-4-d; Box 4: Miscellaneous 1, #187
    - Man in canoe on water, n.d.; 13:2-4-e; Box 4: Miscellaneous 1, #188
    - Group portrait, Mashfer Indians, 13:2-4-f; Box 4: Miscellaneous 1, #189
    - Landscape, North Dakota, 13:2-4-g; Box 4: Miscellaneous 1, #190
    - Ocean, n.d.; 13:2-4-h; Box 4: Miscellaneous 1, #191
    - Martha's Vineyard, n.d.; 13:2-4-i; Box 4: Miscellaneous 1, #192
    - Mountains, n.d.; 13:2-4-j; Box 4: Miscellaneous 1, #193
    - Landscape, 13:2-4-k; Box 4: Miscellaneous 1, #194
    - Leopard skin, n.d.; 13:2-4-l; Box 4: Miscellaneous 1, 195
    - Building, n.d.; 13:2-4-m; Box 4: Miscellaneous 1, #196
    - Sculpture, n.d.; 13:2-4-n; Box 4: Miscellaneous 1, #197
    - Feeding the chickens, n.d.; 13:2-4-o; Box 4: Miscellaneous 1, #198
    - Indian picnic, 13:2-4-p; Box 4: Miscellaneous 1, #199
    - Choctaw village, Louisiana, n.d.; 13:2-4-q; Box 4: Miscellaneous 1, #200
    - Machapunga Indians, North Carolina, 1924; 13:2-5-a; Box 5: Miscellaneous 1, #201
    - Native American man, n.d.; 13:2-5-b; Box 5: Miscellaneous 1, 202
    - Rattles, n.d.; 13:2-5-c; Box 5: Miscellaneous 1, #203
    - Corn cob rattle, n.d.; 13:2-5-d; Box 5: Miscellaneous 1, #204
    - Trap, n.d.; 13:2-5-e; Box 5: Miscellaneous 1, #205
    - Landscape, 13:2-5-f; Box 5: Miscellaneous 1, #206
    - Landscape, 13:2-5-g; Box 5: Miscellaneous 1, #207
    - Forest, n.d.; 13:2-5-h; Box 5: Miscellaneous 1, #208
    - Native American man hunting bear, n.d.; 13:2-5-i; Box 5: Miscellaneous 1, #209
    - Native American man wearing head dress, child holding spear, n.d.; 13:2-5-j; Box 5: Miscellaneous 1, #210
    - Native American man with tomahawk, n.d.; 13:2-5-l; Box 5: Miscellaneous 1, #212
    - Native American woman, n.d.; 13:2-5-m; Box 5: Miscellaneous 1, #213
    - School children, group portrait, n.d.; 13:2-5-n; Box 5: Miscellaneous 1, #214
    - Map of Lake Oneida?, New York, n.d.; 13: 2-5-o; Box 5: Miscellaneous 1, #215
    - Mound, Ferguson farm, Governor Island, North Carolina, 13:2-5-p; Box 5: Miscellaneous 1, #216
    - Map of Indian tribes of the Lower Mississippi, 1909; 13: 2-5-q; Box 5: Miscellaneous 1, #217
    - Mohegan woman, 1909-1932; 13:2-6-a; Box 5; Mohegan, #218
    - Mohegan girl, 1909-1932; 13:2-6-b; Box 5: Mohegan, #219
    - Mohegan man in native attire, 1909-1932; 13:2-6-c; Box 5: Mohegan, #220
    - Mohegan men, women, children, 1909-1932; 13:2-6-d; Box 5: Mohegan, #221
    - Mohegan woman, 1909-1932; 13:2-6-e; Box 5: Mohegan, #222
    - Mohegan man with mortar and pestle, 1909-1932; 13: 2-6-f; Box %; Mohegan, #223
    - Wigwam at Fall festival, 1903; 13:2-6-g; Box 5: Mohegan, #224
    - Mohegan woman, 1909-1932; 13:2-6-h; Box 5: Mohegan, #225
    - Dwelling, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #226
    - Montagnais hunter with dog team, Lake St. John, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #227
    - Montagnais-Naskapi woman, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #228
    - Snowshoes, nets, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #229
    - Montagnais-Naskapi woman, children, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #230
    - Montagnais-Naskapi man in canoe, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #231
    - Montagnais-Naskapi woman, children, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #232, #259
    - Landscape, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #233
    - Landscape, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #234
    - Montagnais-Naskapi women, children, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #237
    - Montagnais-Naskapi men with bear, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #238
    - Canoe, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #239
    - Winter landscape, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #240
    - Winter settlement, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #241
    - Landscape, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #235
    - Dwelling, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #236
    - Montagnais-Naskapi man with bow, arrow, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #242
    - Landscape, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #243
    - Tree, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #244
    - Landscape, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #245
    - Winter landscape, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #246
    - Landscape, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #247
    - Montagnais-Naskapi man, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #248
    - Montagnais-Naskapi children, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #249
    - Settlement, 1908-1941; Box 5: Montagnais-Naskapi, #250
    - Winter landscape, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #251
    - Montagnais-Naskapi boy, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #252
    - Montagnais-Naskapi man, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #253
    - Montagnais-Naskapi boy, girl, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #254
    - Dwelling, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #255
    - Montagnais-Naskapi man, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #256
    - Landscape, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #257
    - Montagnais-Naskapi boys, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #258
    - Dwellings, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #260
    - Dwelling, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #261
    - Canoes, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #262
    - Dwelling, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #263
    - Dwelling, interior, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #264
    - Montagnais-Naskapi men, women, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #265
    - Pole structure, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #266
    - Students, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #267
    - Abenaquis, group portrait, Odanak, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #268
    - Winter landscape, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #269
    - Montagnais-Naskapi girls, Moisie, P.Q., 1914; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #270
    - Landscape, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #271
    - Island, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #272
    - Montagnais-Naskapi boy with rabbit skin hat, Lake St. John, 1914; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #273
    - Shoreline, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #274
    - Montagnais-Naskapi man, three women, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #275
    - Montagnais-Naskapi man with tobaggan, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #276
    - Montagnais-Naskapi group with bear, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #277
    - Winter settlement, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #278
    - Montagnais-Naskapi boys, group portrait, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #279
    - Montagnais-Naskapi group with dogs, 1925; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #280
    - Montagnais-Naskapi boy, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #281
    - Montagnais-Naskapi man, dwelling, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #282
    - Winter camp, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #283
    - Montagnais-Naskapi man, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #284
    - Landscape, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #285
    - Landscape, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #286
    - Island, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #287
    - Montagnais-Naskapi boys in canoe, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #288
    - Montagnais-Naskapi man, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #289
    - Cape Eternity, Canada, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #290
    - Montagnais-Naskapi boy with crossbow, Lake St. John, P.Q., 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #291
    - Malek Begin, Lake St. John, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #292
    - Montagnais-Naskapi woman with baby in sack, 1920; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #293
    - Montagnais-Naskapi boy, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #294
    - Montagnais-Naskapi woman, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #295
    - Reindeer, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #296
    - Montagnais-Naskapi boys, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #297
    - Montagnais-Naskapi woman outside dwelling, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #298
    - Montagnais-Naskapi man, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #299, #304
    - Montagnais-Naskapi woman, 1908-1941; Box 6: Montagnais-Naskapi, #300
    - Montagnais-Naskapi family, 1908-1941; Box 7: Montagnais-Naskapi, #301
    - Montagnais-Naskapi man, 1908-1941; Box 7: Montagnais-Naskapi, #302
    - Montagnais-Naskapi man with dog, winter settlement, 1908-1941; Box 7: Montagnais-Naskapi, #303
    - Montagnais-Naskapi man, 1908-1941; Box 7: Montagnais-Naskapi, #305
    - Montagnais-Naskapi man, 1908-1941; Box 7: Montagnais-Naskapi, #306
    - Map of Quebec, Native American tribal bands, 1908-1941; Box 7: Montagnais-Naskapi, #307
    - Landscape, 1908-1941; Box 7: Montagnais-Naskapi, #308